Anjanee Sail

9930655695 sailanjanee1@gmail.com Mumbai, Maharashtra

Summary

Experienced PHP Developer with over 5 years of experience in IT Industry. Excellent reputation for resolving problems and improving customer satisfaction. Seeking a position to utilize my skills and abilities in that which offers professional growth while being resourceful, innovative and flexible. I will put my best effort to learn the company's policies and make better decisions in the favor of the company.

Experience

Enovate Lifestyle Pvt Ltd

Software Developer, Mumbai, Maharashtra 10/2021 - Present

- Expected Delivery Date Module, Review Module, Book Appintment Module In magento 2.
- Worked closely with other team members to identify and remove software bugs.
- Seeking a position to utilize my skills and abilities in that which offers professional growth while being resourceful, innovative and flexible. I will put my best effort to learn the company's policies and make better decisions in the favor of the company.
- Collected and examined user feedback to improve capacity of software.
- Integration Rest API in Magento 2

Omnificent Technologies Pvt Ltd

Senior Software Engineer, Mumbai, Maharashtra 07/2020 - 10/2021

- Reviewed project specifications and designed technology solutions that met or exceeded performance expectations.
- Discussed project progress with customers, collected feedback on different stages and directly addressed concerns.

Pulse Solutions

Senior Web Developer, Mumbai, Maharashtra 01/2020 - 04/2020

- Multi-tasked across multiple functions and roles to generate project results and meet deadlines and organizational expectations.
- Applied latest emerging technology, software and project application trends to update and maintain site applicability.
- Collaborated with marketing department to determine organizational need and design pages to meet goals.
- Pulled from PHP, SQL, JavaScript and other back-end library knowledge to bolster programming resources.

Finoux Solution Pvt Ltd

Software Engineer, Mumbai, Maharashtra 12/2018 - 07/2019

- Designed and implemented PHP Code Igniter solutions as per project specifications
- Building frontend features using HTML/CSS
- Advanced knowledge of PHP running on Linux systems
- Strong with JavaScript and CSS including Ajax, XML, incremental page loading, etc
- Created Admin Section to handle Backend Functionality

- Working on website lamp, apache
- Basic Linux command line experience and shell scripting in Linux.

The sublimity Pvt Ltd

PHP Developer, Mumbai, Maharashtra 05/2018 - 11/2018

- · Work on a number of varied web development projects within an established development team
- Work with onsite Manager and report proper status
- Resolve / conflict management within team
- Take daily status of project, discuss issues, provide solutions, fix issues
- · Provide expert level abilities in coding, database design, development, and enhancement.

Kredence Technologies Solutions Pvt Ltd

PHP Developer, Mumbai, Maharashtra 11/2017 - 05/2018

- GST, PMS, ITR and generate the PDF form 16.
- Store data in database, add, edit, update and delete.

eTrack Media Pvt Ltd

PHP Web Developer, Mumbai, Maharashtra 01/2016 - 11/2017

- Based on PHP Framework CodeIgniter and technology use Ajax, and MySQL Database.
- Admin can update and delete all details of school as well as student upload the exam result and modify the fess structure
- Admin can upload the PDF file which user can view the front end all report are Generated in excel file. Admin can download the excel file.
- Create new CMS page, blog, widgets.
- Customize the invoice structure, email configuration and customize the category and product page.
- Set shipping rules and tax rules for the product, Based on E-commerce open sources Magento.

Education

BSCIT

M.L. Dahanukar College, Mumbai, Maharashtra 04/2015

HSC

Nirmala Junior College, Mumbai, Maharashtra 04/2012

SSC

Samata Vidya Mandir, Mumbai, Maharashtra 04/2010

Skills

PHP, Codeigniter, Magento, CSS, HTML, AJAX, JQuery, REST API, GraphQL, WordPress, MySQL

Languages

English, Hindi, Marathii